const STORE = [ {
    question: 'Who is the author of the Great Gatspy?',
    answers: [
        'A - John Lennon',
        'B - F. Scott Fitzgerald',
        'C - Jay Gatspy',
        'D - Zelda Fitzgerald',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1, 
},
{
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a book by James Baldwin',
    answers: [
    'A - If Beale Street Could Talk',
    'B - Notes of a Native Son',
    'C The Fire Next to Me',
    'D - The Color Purple',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
},
{
    question: 'What is the Address of the character Sherlock Holmes',
    answers: [
    'A - 42 Wallaby Way',
    'B - 30 Rockefeller Plaza',
    'C - 32 Windsor Gardens',
    'D - 221B Baker Street',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
},
{
    question: 'Who is the narrator of the novel On The Road',
    answers: [
    'A - Neal Cassady',
    'B - Sal Paradise',
    'C - Dean Moriarty',
    'D - Carlo Marx',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
},
{
    question: 'What year did George Orwell publish his book 1984',
    answers: [
    'A - 1949',
    'B - 1982',
    'C - 1984',
    'D - 2002',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
},
{
    question: 'What day of the year does the book Ulysses take place?',
    answers: [
    'A - June 11th',
    'B - March 1st',
    'C - June 16th',
    'D - November 5th',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
},
{
    question: 'Who wrote the novel Slaughterhouse Five?',
    answers: [
    'A - J.R.R. Tolkien',
    'B - Aldous Huxley',
    'C - George Orwell',
    'D - Kurt Vonnegut',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
},
{
    question: 'Which novel opens and closes with the letters of Robert Walton?',
    answers: [
    'A - World of Walton',
    'B - Dracula',
    'C - Alice in Wonderland',
    'D - Frankenstein',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
},
{
    question: 'Where does the novel the Outsiders take place?',
    answers: [
    'A - Dallas',
    'B - Wichita',
    'C - Tulsa',
    'D - Kansas City',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,

},
{
    question: "What was Mark Twain's real name?",
    answers: [
    'A - Tom Sawyer',
    'B - Henry Rodgers',
    'C - Samuel Clemens',
    'D - Mark Twain',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
}
];